{
    "games": [
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "apr\u00e8s",
                    "content": [
                        " afterward",
                        " cycling",
                        " sailing",
                        " indoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "parc d'attractions",
                    "content": [
                        " amusement park ",
                        " enroll in",
                        " sewing",
                        " DIY "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "attraction",
                    "content": [
                        " outdoor",
                        " crafts",
                        " keep fit ",
                        " attraction"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "avant",
                    "content": [
                        " trail",
                        " jog",
                        " beforehand",
                        " gardening "
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "jeu de soci\u00e9t\u00e9",
                    "content": [
                        " season ticket",
                        " board game ",
                        " beforehand",
                        " outdoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "\u00e9checs",
                    "content": [
                        " eat out",
                        " gardening ",
                        " chess",
                        " outdoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "collectionner",
                    "content": [
                        " sailing",
                        " hike",
                        " season ticket",
                        " collect"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "travaux manuels",
                    "content": [
                        " relax",
                        " energetic",
                        " crafts",
                        " outdoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "cyclisme",
                    "content": [
                        " sewing",
                        " indoor",
                        " energetic",
                        " cycling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "bricolage",
                    "content": [
                        " subscription",
                        " keep fit ",
                        " collect",
                        " DIY "
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "manger au restaurant",
                    "content": [
                        " season ticket",
                        " board game ",
                        " energetic",
                        " eat out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "\u00e9nergique",
                    "content": [
                        " energetic",
                        " sewing",
                        " work out",
                        " crafts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "s'inscrire \u00e0",
                    "content": [
                        " enroll in",
                        " chess",
                        " jog",
                        " board game "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "jardinage",
                    "content": [
                        " collect",
                        " gardening ",
                        " jog",
                        " indoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "randonner",
                    "content": [
                        " jog",
                        " hike",
                        " outdoor",
                        " work out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "int\u00e9rieur",
                    "content": [
                        " enroll in",
                        " indoor",
                        " outdoor",
                        " keep fit "
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "ext\u00e9rieur",
                    "content": [
                        " collect",
                        " jog",
                        " outdoor",
                        " crafts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "faire du jogging",
                    "content": [
                        " energetic",
                        " sewing",
                        " relax",
                        " jog"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "garder la forme",
                    "content": [
                        " work out",
                        " attraction",
                        " keep fit ",
                        " sewing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "se reposer",
                    "content": [
                        " relax",
                        " sewing",
                        " chess",
                        " gardening "
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "voile",
                    "content": [
                        " attraction",
                        " sailing",
                        " cycling",
                        " relax"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "abonnement",
                    "content": [
                        " outdoor",
                        " cycling",
                        " indoor",
                        " season ticket"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "couture",
                    "content": [
                        " season ticket",
                        " DIY ",
                        " sewing",
                        " indoor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "abonnement",
                    "content": [
                        " energetic",
                        " beforehand",
                        " DIY ",
                        " subscription"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "sentier",
                    "content": [
                        " collect",
                        " trail",
                        " crafts",
                        " relax"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "faire de l'exercice",
                    "content": [
                        " work out",
                        " sewing",
                        " outdoor",
                        " chess"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}